Finding Aid for Extension Service (University of Michigan) publications, 1911-1996
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Publications
  - Service Center for the Thumb Area 1952-1953 (Box 17)
  - Servicio de Educacion de Obreros
    - Newsletters
      - Noticias Interamericanas, 1945 (Box 17)
  - Six Evenings with the Professors, Undated, 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - STAPP Car Crash Conference, 1970-1978 (Box 17)
  - State Property Fire Safety Seminar, 1958-1962 (Box 17)
  - Student Leadership Training Workshop, 1973-1980 (Box 17)
  - Symposium on Remote Sensing of Environment, 1966-1979, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Tax Practitioner Institute, 1978-1990 (Box 17)
  - Training Seminar for EMS Instructors/Coordinators, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
  - University of Michigan Community College Day, 1975-1976 (Box 17)
  - University of Michigan Medical Center 1963-1966 (Box 17)
  - University of Michigan Night, 1959-1963 (Box 17)
  - Upper Peninsula Clergy Conference, 1967-1977 (Box 17)
  - Upper Peninsula Conference on Aging, 1956-1957 (Box 17)
  - Upper Peninsula Conference on Student Publications, 1956-1969 (Box 17)
  - Upper Peninsula Crafts Exhibit and Conference, 1960-1965 (Box 17)
  - Upper Peninsula Pastor's Conference, 1959-1966 (Box 17)
  - Upper Peninsula Transportation Conference, 1954-1959 (Box 17)
  - War and Postwar Problem Series, 1945 (Box 17)
  - Washtenaw District Nurses Association 1965-1968 (Box 17)
  - A Weekend with the Professors, 1966-1973 (Box 17)
  - Workshop in Outdoor Education, 1975-1980 (Box 17)
  - Workshop in Religious Education, 1946-1948 (Box 17)
  - Workshops for Occupational Education Administrators, 1971-1972 (Box 17)
  - YMCA 1962-1971 (Box 17)
  - Your Conference and the University of Michigan, Undated, 1974-1976 (Box 17)
  - Your Estate and Tax "Reform", 1978 (Box 17)